Small Town Christmas is a drama, romance, tv movie
film directed by Maclain Nelson.
Author Nell Phillips’ first book has become a surprise
best-seller of the Christmas season.
Nell’s last stop on a nationwide book tour takes her to the town of Springdale, the hometown of Emmett Turner, a young
man she met over five years ago while both were junior copy editors at a New York publishing company.
Nell was hurt when Emmett stood her up for a dinner date and then
disappeared from New York without any explanation.
As Nell is quick to admit, Emmett’s colorful, nostalgic anecdotes about Springdale inspired her
to write this book that is shaping her life and especially this holiday season.
Emmett Turner, played by Kristoffer Polaha.
Nell Phillips, played by Ashley Newbrough.
Steve, played by Ryan McDonell.
Stacy, played by Nhi Do.
Hayley, played by Debs Howard.
Marnie, played by Bailey Skodje.
Seuss' The Grinch (or simply The Grinch) is a 2018 American animated
Christmas comedy film based on How the Grinch Stole Christmas!
Produced by Illumination, it was directed by Scott Mosier and Yarrow
Cheney and written by Michael LeSieur and Tommy Swerdlow.
Narrated by Pharrell Williams, the film stars Benedict Cumberbatch as the Grinch, with
Rashida Jones, Kenan Thompson, and Angela Lansbury in supporting roles.
The plot follows the Grinch, who plans to stop Whoville's Christmas celebration by
stealing all the town's decorations and gifts, with his pet dog Max.
The film is the third screen adaptation of the book, following the
1966 television special and the 2000 live-action film.
It was announced in 2013, and by 2016, Cumberbatch was cast, and
Cheney and Peter Candeland were set to direct.
In 2018, Mosier took over Candeland's position as co-director.
Danny Elfman composed the score, with a song written
and performed by Tyler, the Creator.
The Grinch was released in the United States on November 9, 2018, by Universal.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and grossed $540 million, becoming the
highest-grossing Christmas film in history, as well as the highest-grossing Dr.
Seuss film adaptation.
The film explores themes of small town, holiday, author, christmas.
The tone is emotional.